NGUYEN BA LOCJAVA DEVELOPER

05/04/1994

SUMMARY

I have 4 years of work experience in software development (3 year with Java and 1 year with t24 core banking

I have experience and strong at Software and Web Application using Java

I expect to a young and comfortable environment in next company and i expect to giving at all to my next company

Strong:

- quickly follow the projects
- Successful completion of assigned projects
- Ouick and effective
- Ability to self-study and team work
- High ability to learn

Weakness:

Business of Project

WORK EXPERIENCE

Usol Company | 07/2017 - 01/2019 Java software development

Responsibilities

- Maintain and develop a website to manage progress and quality of work as same as jira (product of company)
- Complete parts of work as assigned by leader and BA
- Fix issue in progress and quality reports
- Develop the function of reporting progress by day, month and year
- Develop the function to export progress reports
- Fix code seleninum automation test of old version to new version
- Develop the function import file excel of quantity reports to browser

Technologies:

Spring MVC, Selenium, Postgresql, SQL Server, VBA (excel tool), JQuery, Javascript, CSS as same as Boostrap

IIST Company | 02/2019 - 04/2020 Java software development

Responsibilities

Onsite Viettel Keangnam 40 floors for 6 month

- Develop and maintain of viettel broadcasting station management project
- Create, Edit, Measure the position of broadcasting stations
- Move database from oracle to maria database
- Maintain the function of synchronizing database data of viettel "Disaster Prevention Project"
- Fix automatic disaster relief vehicle location update function
- Develop web service functionality that retrieves data from another system using SOAP UI

Join offshore team projects

- -Developmentofautomotivemanagementprojectfunctions related to proposal
- + Functional activity development : ask for funding to repair and maintain cars from superiors
- Develop the functionality of the "Electronic Invoice" project
- + Function Find, add new categories of category
- Join "Procurement Portal" project
- + Export reports on investment projects as same as Parent category, subcategory, volume of broadcasting station related works
- Join "Asset Treasure project"
- + Develop the function to update the volume of the warehouse
- + Export data of items stored in the warehouse
- + Update the item's number of items when the contract are partially used

Technologies:

Spring Data JPA, Hibernate, PrimeFace, Java JSF, Web service, Microservice

Paraline Company | 05/2020 - 06/2021 Core banking development

Responsibilities

Onsite in MB Bank 18 Le Van Luong Street, Trung Kinh Ward, Ha Noi City

- Participating in the bank's core bank development project
- + Module Deposit Account such as Children Saving Account, Smart Saving Account, Module Loans and Deposit, Module FundsTransfer, Module Collateral and internal improvements of MB's T24 core banking
- + Participate in the project of upgrading T24 core baking from R16 to R20 (Teminos application for C -> Teminos Application for Java)

Technologies:

C, Java

One Mount (Vin Group) | 07/2021 - Present BE Java Developer

Responsibilities

- Onsite in Techcombank at 191 Ba Trieu Street, Le Dai Hanh Ward, Hai Ba Trung District, Ha Noi
- Develop based on the requirements of Techcombank: Rework application Fast Mobile using BackBase technology, using Microservervice Netflix, Eureka Client, Spring Cloud Config, Spring Hibernate, Spring Data JPA, Spring Specification, using Java 8 to find data (Lambda).

Technologies:

BackBase technology, using Microservervice Netflix, Eureka Client, Spring Cloud Config, Spring Hibernate, Spring Data JPA, Spring Specification, using Java 8 to find data (Lambda), Docker, Kubernetes

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Java Core
Java Spring Boot
JQuery
HTML & CSS
Core Banking
SOAP
JavaScript
Microservices
Docker
Kubernetes

EDUCATION

University Of Transport Technology | 08/2014 - 01/2019

Major: Information System Graduated with a good degree

Aprotrain Aptech | 10/2012 - 12/2014 Major: Information Technology